

Profile

Passionate Content Writer with an eye for attention to detail. My leadership skills and my continuous stress upon hard work and dedication complement my desire for team success. I love English literature. Science fiction is my favourite genre. Journalism has always been a keen interest of mine. I have vast experience in blog, article and editorial/column writing. Good command on SEO. I have also had experience in social media management.

Employment History

Website Manager at Daily Business News, Lahore + Multan Jan, 2021 - Mar, 2021

Co-Head at Social Media team, Computer Science Society, Comsats, Islamabad

Sep, 2020 - Present

Senior Editor at Orfik, Islamabad

Jan, 2020 - Nov, 2020

Content writer at Daily Business News

Jan, 2021 - Mar, 2021

Content writer at Daxno, Islamabad

Dec 2021 - Present

Education

Matriculation at Nishat Girls High School, MULTAN

Sep 2021 - Sep 2021

Fsc at Kips College for girls, MULTAN

Aug, 2018 - Apr, 2020

Bachelors in Software Engineering at Comsats University,

Islamabad

Aug, 2020 - Present

Other

IMUN

Dec, 2020 - Dec, 2020

Took part in IMUN ONLINE CONFERENCE, 5-6 December.

Details

noorfatima122001@gmail.com

Contact me on my Email address or LinkedIn.

Multan 66000, Pakistan

Links

LinkedIn

Portfolio

Skills

Communication

Content Writing

SEO Optimization

Leadership

Management

Coding

Languages

Urdu

English

Hobbies

Reading

Travelling